import "Catalog/catalog.css";


// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/gb.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],
}


export var cards = {
  '0': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Zéro',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'zero'
  },
  '1': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Un',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'one'
  },
  '3': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Trois',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'three'
  },  '4': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Quatre',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'four'
  },
  '5': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Cinq',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'five'
  },
  '6': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Six',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'six'
  },
  '7': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Sept',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'seven'
  },
  '8': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Huit',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'eight'
  },
  '9': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Neuf',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'nine'
  },
  '10': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Dix',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'ten'
  },
  '11': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Onze',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'eleven'
  },
  '12': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Douze',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'twelve'
  },
  '13': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Treize',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'thirteen'
  },
  '14': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Quatorze',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'fourteen'
  },
  '15': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Quinze',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'fifteen'
  },
  '16': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Seize',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'sixteen'
  },
  '17': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Dix-sept',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'seventeen'
  },
  '18': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Dix-huit',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'eighteen'
  },
  '19': {
    type: 'text',
    question: 'Dix-neuf',
    prompt: 'Ce nombre en anglais ?',
    answer: 'nineteen'
  }
};
